{
    "subject": "Bert_Haanstra",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Fanfare__film_",
    "human_readable": "Bert Haanstra created the film Fanfare.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9863228797912598,
            "question": "Did Bert Haanstra create a film titled Fanfare?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9723653793334961,
            "question": "Was Fanfare directed by Bert Haanstra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9433172345161438,
            "question": "Name a film created by Bert Haanstra."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8783662915229797,
            "question": "What artistic medium did Bert Haanstra use to create Fanfare?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8663790822029114,
            "question": "What is the name of the film created by Bert Haanstra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8027758598327637,
            "question": "Can you name a film created by an artist named Bert Haanstra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7114859819412231,
            "question": "What type of work did Bert Haanstra create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7011930346488953,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Bert Haanstra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6513044834136963,
            "question": "Who directed the film Fanfare?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3546401262283325,
            "question": "Is Fanfare a novel, a painting, or a film?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Bert Haanstra created the film Fanfare.",
            "html": "yago_11081_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who directed the film Fanfare?",
            "html": "yago_11081_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the title of the film directed by Bert Haanstra?",
            "html": "yago_11081_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of work did Bert Haanstra create?",
            "html": "yago_11081_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11081_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11081_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11081_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11081_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11081_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11081_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11081_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11081_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11081_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11081_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Bert Haanstra released the film \"Fanfare\" in 1958, which supports the statement that he created this film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}